Guide to the George Nicolau Papers WAG.250
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
George Nicolau Papers
circa 1970-2013
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Nicolau, George
WAG.250
24 Linear Feet in 23 record cartons and 2 manuscript boxes.
This collection consists of attorney George Nicolau's arbitration decisions and awards. George Nicolau has worked as a labor arbitrator since the 1970s, most notably serving as the chief arbitrator for Major League Baseball from 1986 to 1995. Nicolau's arbitration decisisons are mostly dated between 1970 and 2010, and cover a variety of trades including the airline, entertainment, communications, health, and sports industries.
Biographical Note
George Nicolau (born 1925) is a veteran labor arbitrator and attorney. After serving in the Second World War as a bomber navigator in the 8th Air Force, he began practicing law. In the mid-1960s, he worked for the federal government in the administration of the Peace Corps and Office of Economic Opportunity.
By the 1970s, Nicolau was mostly working as an arbitrator, a profession he continues to practice after his official retirement. He is most famous for being the chief arbitrator for Major League Baseball from 1986 to 1995. However, his arbitration spans many fields, including the airline, entertainment, health, and sports industries.
Arrangement
This collection has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials from the first accession contains arbitrations files, which are indexed and arranged either alphabetically or by union. The files from the accretion in 2013 are grouped thematically by trade and described at the box-level. The container list may not reflect folder labels, but rather folder contents.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the arbitration opinions and awards of arbitrator George Nicolau. The files in this collection address a wide variety of labor disputes with particular concentrations in entertainment, airline, education, communications, and health unions.
An additional donation of arbitration awards was added to the collection in 2013. These materials center heavily on airline and basketball disputes, but also contain awards relating to broadcasting, health care, maritime, communications, theatre, and transportation unions. The majority of these decisions date between 1990 and 2010.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by George Nicolau in 2002. The accession number associated with this gift is 2002.014. An additional donation was made in 2013. The accession number associated with this gift is 2013.043.
Arbitration (Administrative law); Arbitration files.; Arbitration decisions.; Arbitration and award.; Labor laws and legislation.; Collective labor agreements -- Lawyers.; Grievance arbitration.; Nicolau, George; National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians; American Broadcasting Company; National Broadcasting Company; Major League Baseball Players Association; Communications Workers of America; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers; Transport Workers Union of America.; Workmen's Circle (U.S.). Home for the Aged of New York State (Bronx, New York, N.Y.); Service Employees International Union. Local 1199 (New York, N.Y.)
- Adelphi, 363480 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- AFMA Castle Rock / Shani Films (Shawshank Redemption), 363479 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- AFM / Livent, 363478 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- AFTRA / ABC (0863 84) Retroactive Payments, 363477 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- NBC / AFTRA (News Assistants), 363476 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- AFTRA & National Broadcasting Company, 363475 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- AFTRA / Unity Broadcasting, 363474 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- AFTRA / Yaffe (1373-87 Bruce), 363473 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- AFTRA / ABC (Santos 1461 86), 363472 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Allied Services Division BRAC / Handing Services, Inc. 0123-84, 363471 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- H.N.S. / ATU, Local 420 (0025195; Colon), 363470 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- APSCUF / State 1338 92Q, 363469 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Bakery Local 50 / McIntyre, 363468 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Baltimore Firefighters, 363467 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Barnard TWUA, 363466 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Beacon Board of Ed. and Beacon Teachers Assn. (Class Size), 363465 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Beacon Teachers and Beacon City School District (Class Size II), 363464 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Bedford Teachers Assn. and Bedford Board of Education, 363463 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Bellmore TA (0374 83), 363462 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Black Network / NABET (0194 82), 363461 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Bloomingdales (2000 85), 363460 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- BOCES (0342-82), 363459 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Boston Edison / UWUA (2055-87), 363458 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Boston Teachers Union, AFL-CIO / Boston School Committee, 363457 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Boston PBA and City of Boston (1139-0015-74 Re: OBrien), 363456 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Boston Teachers and Boston School Comm. (Mooney, Flaherty, & Logan), 363455 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Boston Teachers Union and Boston School Committee Griev.: James Mahoney, 363454 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Brookhaven / IBEW, 363453 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Brookhaven / IBEW (Yanofsky), 363452 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Assoc. Universities (Brookhaven National Laboratory / IBEW, Local 2230, 363451 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- IBT, L. 804 / Brinkmann, 363450 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Byram Hills Teachers Assn. and BD of ED (Insurance I.D.), 363449 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- CBS/AFTRA (0589), 363448 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- CBS / IBEW (082284 Margiotta), 363447 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Cambridge Teachers Association / Cambridge School Committee 0296-75, 363446 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- CBS IBEW L 1212 (01161 93; Termination of George Petrillo), 363445 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- CBS / IATSE L. 1, 363444 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- CBS / IBEW L. 1212 (0019-72), 363443 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- CBS / SAG (50th Anniversary Special), 363442 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Carborundum Company / OCAW Local 8-490, 363441 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- CIR / HHC (A-3733-91), 363440 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- CIR/ NYC Health & Hosp. Corp. (A-565-76 Lincoln Hospital), 363439 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Columbia Univ. / TWU, 363438 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Council 82, AFSCME, AFL-CIO (Raymond Fletcher and Roy Warner / NY State, 363437 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Continental Baking Co. / Bakery Drivers Local 550, IBT (2029-85), 363436 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- CSX / BMWE (SBA 1096), 363435 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- CUNY / Local 3 IBEW, 363434 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Curtiss Wright / IAM (86K.03769), 363433 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Curtiss Wright / IAM )87-19829), 363432 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- CWA / Bd. of Ed. (Snow Days), 363431 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Daily News / Local 6 NYTU, 363430 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Daily News / Local 6 NYTU (shift guarantees), 363429 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Dannon / IBT 584 (1378; Spencer and Meany), 363428 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Dannon IBT L. 584 (NJ Center; 1300 86), 363427 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Denver Schools (0047 92), 363426 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Denver / DCTA (0027 95; Charles Todesco), 363425 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Denver Schools/ ATU (Espinoza), 363424 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Depository Trust / L 153, Office and Professional Employees International Union, AFL-CIO 01675 92, 363423 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- DGA / CBS, 363422 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- DGA / NBC (AVID), 363421 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- DOC / Woodhull (1433 96), 363420 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- DC 37 / NYPL 1662-81, 363419 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Queensboro Public Library / Local 1321, District Council #37, 363418 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Art Steel Company / District 65 Wholesale, Retail, and Office Processing Union (Martinez Discharge), 363417 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Art Steel Compnany / District 65 Wholesale, Retail, and Office Processing Union (Re: Jose L. Cruz), 363416 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- District 65 Wholesale, Retail, and Office Processing Union / Fabrics Around the World, 363415 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Four Continent Book Corporation / District 65, 363414 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- District 65 / Glass Masters, 363413 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Tuschman / District 65 (Re: Abe Gottlieb), 363412 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- NYPL / DC 371552-81, 363411 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- MAC-LOU Mens and Boys Wear / District 65 Retail Wholesale Office and Processing Union, 363410 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- District Council 1707 AFSCME, AFL-CIO / American Jewish Congress, 363409 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- D.C. 1707 / Development Corporation for Israel 0523 88, 363408 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- DC 1707 / Jewish Community Services of Long Island 00900 91, 363407 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- District 1707 and Seven Corners Day Care Center (Cynthia Cummins), 363406 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- DC 1707 / New York Association for New Americans, Inc. (00768 91), 363405 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Mobilization for Youth / Local 1707, Community and Social Agency, 363404 (Box 1, Folder 77)
- D.C. 37 / NYC Health and Hospital Corporation (A-468-75 Griev. of L. Bush), 363403 (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Local 1707, Community and Social Agency Employees Union / Mobilization for Youth (2nd Case), 363402 (Box 1, Folder 79)
- Office and Professional Employees Union / DeLeval Separator Co., 363401 (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Local 1, AJDWWU and Designcraft Jewel Industries (Article XXXII), 363400 (Box 1, Folder 81)
- Doctors Council / OLR, 363399 (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Doctors Council / Office of Municipal Labor Relations (1489 82), 363398 (Box 1, Folder 83)
- Doctors Council / Woodhull, 363397 (Box 1, Folder 84)
- Dept. of Labor / National Council of Field Labor Locals, Local 2513, 363396 (Box 1, Folder 85)
- Dow Jones / IAPE (0594 86), 363395 (Box 1, Folder 86)
- Drake Bakeries / L. 50 Bakery, Confectionary & Tobacco Workers Union, 363394 (Box 1, Folder 87)
- East Brunswick School / EBEA (04394 Esposito & Kochanski), 363393 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Ellenville Central School District / Ellenville Teachers Association, 363392 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Exxon Chemical / Bayway ESU (00182 94L), 363391 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Exxon Marine / Exxon Shipping Company, Costal Division (Termination of Tug Boat Stewards), 363390 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Fairchild / IBEW Local 25 (025684), 363389 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Federal Aviation Administration / National Association of Government Employees, Local R2-73 (76K07099), 363388 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Motion Picture Editors, Local 771, IATSE / Calvin Schultz, 363387 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Franklin Square Teachers Association / Franklin Square Union Free School District, 363386 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Furcon / PricewaterhouseCoopers 02607 02, 363385 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Garden City Teachers Association / Garden City Free School District 0184 83, 363384 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Georgia Pacific Corporation / IBT L. 456 (85K/07490), 363383 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- German / Meyers Parking System, Inc. Teamsters Local 917, 363382 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Glen Cove School District / Glen Cove Teachers Assn. (A75-224), 363381 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- GHI / Local 153, Office & Professional Employees (Ruotolo), 363380 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Gouverneur Health Services Program NYU Medical Center / Dist. 1199, National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees 0483-84, 363379 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Goldsmith Motors Corp / UAW Local 259 (01742 91; Layoff of John Pollack), 363378 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Gristede Bros, Inc. / Local 1500, Retail Clerks International Assoc. (Antonio Tesoriero), 363377 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Grossman, Steel & Aluminum Corp. / Shopmens Local Union 455 (0390-74), 363376 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Hansen Teachers Assn. / Hansen School Committee, 363375 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Harrahs Marina Hotel / Local 54 Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (0404 87M), 363374 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Helstoski / Hoebel, 363373 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Village of Hempstead / Patrolmens Benevolent Assoc., 363372 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Hertz Corp / District 15, IAM (Subcontracting), 363371 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Shopmans Local 455 / Highland Steel Fabricators, Inc, 363370 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Hofstra University / Local 100 SEIU, 363369 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Innovative Artists Agency / Velez (SAG), 363368 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- IBEW, L. 3 / L. 153 OPEIU (Appel), 363367 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Imperial Delivery Service / Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York and Vicinity (00890 93), 363366 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- INS / American Federation of Government Employees, Local 1917 (83K/29043), 363365 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- INS / American Federation of Government Employees, Local 1917 (85K/06386 Vassallo), 363364 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Interfaith Medical Center / NY State Fed. Of Physicians and Dentists (00041 97), 363363 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Interfaith / NY State Fed of Physicians and Dentists (01486 96), 363362 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- IOW / Valero (00740 00), 363361 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- International House of Pancakes / L. 650 Chain Restaurant Employees Union (1357 71), 363360 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- ISLIP Teachers Association / ISLIP Board of Education, 363359 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- ITT World Communications, Inc. / Communications Workers of America (51 300 0578 87B), 363358 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Jersey Journal / Newspaper and Mail Deliveries Union, 363357 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Local 100 SEIU / Jeffer Funeral Homes, Inc., 363356 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- United Rubber Workers, Local 266 / Keene Corporation, 363355 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- OPEIU, Local 153 / CSX Lines (02665 1), 363354 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Legal Aid Society / ALLA (Brewer), 363353 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Legal Aid Society / ALLA (Leventhal), 363352 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Legal Services / UAW (Lebron), 363351 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Associated Musicians of Greater New York L. 802 / Howard & Donald (Black and Blue), 363350 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Lockheed Martin / Engineers Union L 444 (444: 97-04), 363349 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Licensed Practical Nurses / Presbyterian Hospital (S. Weiss), 363348 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Licensed Practical Nurses / Presbyterian Hospital (Retroactivity of Vacation Provision), 363347 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Long Island Lighting Company / IBEW L. 1049 (1730-0281-81), 363346 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Long Island Railroad Company / Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (Catapano), 363345 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Local 771, IATSE / ABC (Andresakis), 363344 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Local 771, MPPE / ABC (Discharge of Edward Lempa), 363343 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- L. 802 Associated Musicians of Greater New York / League of American Theatres (Wind in the Willows & The Mystery of Edwin Drood), 363342 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- League of American Theatres and Producers / L. 802 Associated Musicians of Greater New York (Grand Hotel: The Musical), 363341 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Local 802, Assoc. of Musicians of NY / Metropolitan Opera (Syndicated Radio Scales)Local 802, American Federation of Musicians / Metropolitan Opera Assoc. (01572 90); Erica Miner), 363340 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Local 802, American Federation of Musicians / League of New York Theaters & Producers, Inc., Nederlander-Rose Inc., Theater Now, Inc. (0879-84), 363339 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- L. 802, American Federation of Musicians / Metropolitan Opera Association (Howard; 0669-86), 363338 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Local 802, American Federation of Musicians / Universal Dance Orchestras, 363337 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- United Transportation Union and Long Island Railroad (Docket # 75-18), 363336 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- United Transportation Union / Long Island Railroad (Docket 76-10), 363335 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Local 1-S, Retail, Wholesale, Department Store Workers Union, AFL-CIO / Macys (Perf. of Sales Clerk Duties), 363334 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Macys / Local 1-S, Retail, Wholesale, Department Store Workers Union, AFL-CIO (James), 363333 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Macys / Local 804, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, 363332 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Village of Malverne / Malverne PBA (CA-0016; M74-71), 363331 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Metro North / PBA (00107 97; Pagnoni), 363330 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Mobil / IOW (833 97 A), 363329 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- MTL / MGBA (Vanderhorst), 363328 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Museum of Natural History / L. 1306 District Council 37, AFSCME (00214 95; Sumter), 363327 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Metro-North / ARSA Et al., 363326 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- MoMA / Local 32-B, Service Employees International Union, AFL-CIO, 363325 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Monroe-Woodbury Teachers Assn. / Board of Ed (B. Tag), 363324 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Monticello Teachers Assn. and Monticello Board of Ed., 363323 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- William Morris Agency / Scamardella, 363322 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- MSG / AFRTA (00178 99; Robert Page), 363321 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- MSG / IBEW L. 1212 (Rehwinkle; 0203 88), 363320 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- National Pharmacies, Inc. / OCAW, Local 8-406 (0594 90N; Singh), 363319 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- National Carriers Conference Committee / Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 363318 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Needham Educators Assn / Needham School Committee, 363317 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Newark Ledger / IBT, Local 1100, 363316 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Nexans Energy USA / IBEW L. 1430 (FMCS 02-09571), 363315 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Newspaper Guild of NY L. 3 / Time Warner (01245 92), 363314 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- New Jersey State Council of Lathers Health and Welfare Fund, 363313 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- New York Racing Association / Local 30 IUOE, AFL-CIO (22357 97; Belmont Staffing), 363312 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- NYRA / Local 30 IUOE, AFL-CIO (258 97; Ray Martin), 363311 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- NYRA / Local 3, IBEW, 363310 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- New York City Housing Authority and Resident Advisory CCL of NYCHA, 363309 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- NYC Opera / L. 802 American Federation of Musicians (Bruno), 363308 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- NY Times / Newspaper Guild Local 3 (00707 97; Building Cleaning Services Department Pay Rate Dispute), 363307 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- NY Times / Newspaper Guild Local 3 (00035 95; On Call), 363306 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- NY Times / Paper Handlers and Straighteners Union No. 1, 363305 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Northpost UFSD #4 / Local 100 SEIU, AFL-CIO, 363304 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- OCA Asaldi, 363303 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- OCA Campbell 86/161, 363302 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- OCA Christmas Recess, 363301 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- OCA / NYCCA; 93/24, 363300 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- OCA / NYSCOA (Magnetometer Detail), 363299 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- OCA / NYSCCA (McGittigan; 87/35), 363298 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- OCA / NYSCOA, 363297 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- OCA / NYSCCA (Bianchi & Lieberman 86/34 & 35), 363296 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- OCA / JT. Connell (Religious Leave), 363295 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- OCA (Dineen), 363294 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- OCA / S. Ct. (99/6; Signorelli), 363293 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Oderwald / Shopmens local 455 (1898-85), 363292 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- OER / Security Unit Employees, Council 82 (88-69), 363291 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- AFGE, Local 3056 / OEO (FMCS 7K10060; Lloyd), 363290 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- OMLR / CCA (A-2467-86), 363289 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- OLR / PBA (A-3643-91; Queens Task Force), 363288 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- OLR / IBT (Friedman), 363287 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- OLR / SBA (A-3078-89; OT), 363286 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- OMLR / PBA (Kelly), 363285 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- OMLR / PBA (A-2394-86; Marlin), 363284 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- OMLR / PBA (Salzano), 363283 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- OMLR / PBA (A-2518-87; Taylor, 363282 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- OMLR / SBA (Reserve Duty A-2332-40/86), 363281 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- SBA / OMLR (NSU Sergeants), 363280 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- OMLR / UFA (Marshals), 363279 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- UMD Local 333 / OMCR (A-1291-81), 363278 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Otis Elevator / Local 1, International Union of Elevator Constructors (1253 84), 363277 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Patchogue Medford (PERB #A77-34), 363276 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Pearl River Teachers Assn. / Pearl River Union Free School District, 363275 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Pearl River / PRTA, 363274 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Philadelphia Teachers (1973 85Q), 363273 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Local Union #3 IBEW / Picker X-Ray Corp. (R. Scheps), 363272 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Pioneer / UFCW (Thompson), 363271 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Pittsburgh-Des Moines Steel / Local 13 IBBISBFH, 363270 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Pocono Medical Center / JNESCO (172 99), 363269 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Port Authority / Port Authority Police Lieutenants Benevolent Association (1820 92; McGovern & Mackesy), 363268 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Port Authority / DEA (1728 92), 363267 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Port Jefferson Station Teachers / Board of Ed of Comsewogue, UFSD (0346-81), 363266 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Procter Teachers Assn. and Proctor School Board (Rutland, Vermont), 363265 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- PSA / NYSUT (215 84; Peretti), 363264 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Public Service Electric and Gas Co. / IBEW (0496-87S; Campbell), 363263 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- Public Service Electric and Gas Co. / IBEW (0423; Dunn), 363262 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Public Service Electric and Gas Co. / IBEW (0334 88S), 363261 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Public Service Electric and Gas Co. / IBEW (0376 90; Positive Discipline), 363260 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Public Service Electric and Gas Co. / IBEW (0063 94S; Montone), 363259 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Putnam Valley Fed. Of Teachers / Board of Education of Putnam Valley, 363258 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- Putnam Valley Fed. of Teachers / P.V. School District (Hall & Bus Duty), 363257 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Probation Officers / OLMR (Walsh), 363256 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- Reuters / Guild (0297 98; New Attendance and Disciplinary Policy), 363255 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Reuters / Guild (02178 01; Overtime Pay / Alternative Work Arrangements), 363254 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- Reuters / Guild (727 00; Wallace), 363253 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- Roland / NEC and Pinkus (1510-86), 363252 (Box 3, Folder 73)
- RBH / OCAW, Local 8-622 (272 93S), 363251 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- RKO / DGA (137-80), 363250 (Box 3, Folder 75)
- Ridgewood Education Association / Ridgewood Board of Education (119 73D), 363249 (Box 3, Folder 76)
- Rooney / Lowenstein, 363248 (Box 3, Folder 77)
- IBT, Local 804 / Route Messenger Service, Inc. (644 83), 363247 (Box 3, Folder 78)
- Rutgers / Local 888, AFSCME, Council 52 (0049 87N), 363246 (Box 3, Folder 79)
- Rutgers / AFSCME Local 1761 (00342 92L; Scharfenstein), 363245 (Box 3, Folder 80)
- Rutgers / AFSCME Local 1761 (00411 92L; Fitz), 363244 (Box 3, Folder 81)
- SAG / Batten Barton Durstine & Osborne (886-86; Throne), 363243 (Box 3, Folder 82)
- SAG / Butner Advertising (Christie), 363242 (Box 3, Folder 83)
- SAG / Communion Productions (212 80), 363241 (Box 3, Folder 84)
- SAG / De Leeuw Hill and Associates (1281 87), 363240 (Box 3, Folder 85)
- Sanyo / IBT Local 560 (579 92L; Radoslovich), 363239 (Box 3, Folder 86)
- Saugerties Central School District / Saugerties Teachers Association, 363238 (Box 3, Folder 87)
- Scamardella / ABC (0150-84), 363237 (Box 3, Folder 88)
- Sealand OPEIU Local 153 (0542 97N; Bargaining Unit Work), 363236 (Box 3, Folder 89)
- SETPA / TWU Local 234 (1851 88Q; Thomas), 363235 (Box 3, Folder 90)
- Scenic Artists Local 829 / Spofford Beadle, et al. (Butley), 363234 (Box 3, Folder 91)
- Social Security Administration / AFGE, 363233 (Box 3, Folder 92)
- Snyder / CBS (0013 91), 363232 (Box 3, Folder 93)
- SSA / AFGE Local 1760 (81K/24407), 363231 (Box 3, Folder 94)
- SSA / AFGE Local 1760 (88-0658; Clark), 363230 (Box 3, Folder 95)
- South Oaks / Local 1199, Drug, Hospital, & Health Care Employees Union (0120 87), 363229 (Box 3, Folder 96)
- Engineers Union / Sperry Rand Corp. (0551-75), 363228 (Box 3, Folder 97)
- Sperry Rand / IUE, 363227 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Star Ledger / Graphics Communications Union Local 8N (674 98), 363226 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Star Ledger / Graphics Communications Union Local 8N (575 98; Holiday Pay), 363225 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Suburban Propane / IBT, local 338 (81K/14574), 363224 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- BDEU / Suffern Beer Distributors (Re: Discharge of D. Ackerson and M. Saul), 363223 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Utility Workers Union of America / Suffolk County Water Authority, 363222 (Box 4, Folder 6)